thelollingtonpost.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at TheLollingtonPost.com. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for TheLollingtonPost.com.

## Log Files

Like most standard website servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Email Subscription

If a user wishes to subscribe to our posts via email (powered by Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

## Cookies Used

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Our site use cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section.

## Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

## Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to these information. We are currently looking for advertisers.

## Contact Information

If users have any queries regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://thelollingtonpost.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us").
